Ending
Un.
Bumping around.
I'm hungry.
I'm pretty hungry.
Much, much, much.
Is it a hit?
Much more than before.
And a little bit of a heart attack.
This rice cake is warm.
Mochi?
Umegaiimo is warm too.
What's that?
It looks delicious. It looks absolutely delicious.
Let's go!
It's my first time.
What is it? There's something wrong.
FUKUWA.
Good night.
That was close, Akichan.
It's so big!
I'll decorate it.
Cute.
It's a little big, but it's like we're going to wear it.
Wait a minute, isn't this the one you put here on purpose?
Isn't that the one you put up on the wall?
No, they're not on the wall.
You're putting it on the floor?
Sorry, sorry.
Maybe they have frames like that over there, too.
I'll put it back.
Is it prettier on the wall?
Take a picture. The floor is pretty, too.Take a picture. The floor is cute too.
I want to play the lottery!
I wonder if they're there?
Are they already here?
Oh, my God!
Ami's face is amazing.
I want to see it.
I'm gonna go.
Are you sure?
Start the preparations!
Thank you for watching.
They didn't see us.
No, they didn't.
Yes, you did.
They know.
You can't leave Perfection.
He doesn't know. He doesn't know.
They don't know.
Oh!
Aah!
It's funny.
It feels too familiar.
Ooh!
Aah!
Good night.
Thank you.
It takes a while for people to notice.
And they're happy.
They're getting used to it... the space.
Ukiyo kakefish wrapped in (bamboo) leaves
Ukiyoe
Well, I'm back now.
Then I'm already here.
I'm next to the TV shop.
It's starting.
It's just a little while longer.
Are you okay?
What is this place?
This is a soba store, isn't it?
Oh, it's a soba store.
What kind of soba store?
A soba shop.
That one.
That's it, right?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
If you try lighting, don't deviate from the original, or you'll lose the light.
It's a dead end.
It's like there's a lot of vertical space, and it's my favorite.
It's a wide-angle circle. That's fun.
Oh, wow.
T15.
This is a good seat.
The chairs aren't too hard.
Nice.
I haven't left my chair at the lower entrance yet
I haven't left the chair at the lower entrance yet.
Good?
I'm starving.
I've seen it before, but I can already see what we have up our sleeves.
All right.
Let's do it.
I'll do my best.
I've prepared the munchies.
This is the makeup end group.It is a makeup end group.
Muchan bun.
Am egg.
Cute.
Thank you.
Muchan bun.
It's so cute!
Cute.
Dumplings. Cute.
I made dumplings today.
I've always wanted to do that.
The hair style is matching with Nui's.
It smells really good.
I did it.
Why?
We're together, aren't we?
What?
Ni!
Oh, my God, it's making all kinds of animal noises.
Okay, so are we on the opposite team?
Yes!
Good night.
Good night, everyone.
We'll be on our way up shortly.
Good night.
How heavy is it?
I can't hang on without hitting the camera,
Zoopeak
Hey, chickadee.
How'd it go?
I'm going to go with the Loxony type for now.For now, I'm going to go with the Loxony type.
What is it now? I'm fine.
I'm in the zone.
Yes, ma'am.
Ready?
Today, we have a super exciting publicity stunt... the Heart Rock Confort Tour 2023.
Cute, cute, too cute! Thank you very much for coming to
Thank you very much.
Yes, I am. I'm Starkey, aka Aki-chan from the Super Tokimeki Room.
Thank you very much. I have a lot of applause.
Before the show begins, I would like to give you a few words of caution and a request.
Please refrain from taking pictures, recording, or video recording in the venue except during the free recording time.
Cheering in your seats is allowed during the performance.
There are no restrictions on the duration or volume of cheering from your seat,
However, please do not shout in a way that interferes with the performance or disturbs other audience members.
Oh!
Seats in the reserved seating area do not allow standing up to watch the performance.
Please be seated and watch, watch, watch, watch, watch.
Please note that voices that disturb the audience around you are prohibited.
The show will begin shortly.
How are you all doing?
How are you?
Wow! We are very, very, very well.
We love you all. Wait for us!
Nice action!
Here comes the engine.
KANAMI!
JURINA!
HITOKO!
HARUKA!
AKI!
HIYORI!
Chotokimeki Advertising Department!
Rock on!
Good night.Good night.
I'm moving the members.
Okay, good luck.
I'm in. I got a hot hug.
Did you see that?
I saw it. I saw it.
There you are.
I changed my hair. Hair change.
I changed my hair during the show.
Please be careful so that everyone can see.
Sweat tickles a little here.
I'm going to get crumpled up.
I'm off. I'm off.
Thank you all for coming to Love.
Thank you for your hard work!
It was the Osaka show.
It was a great show!
It was a lot of bread.
Pan-pan-pan.
It was so much fun.
And it was like this, right?
Yeah.
So I couldn't see unless it looked really beautiful.
I could see.
Thank you very much.
I was happy that I could do it if I saw you two side by side, even though you could go up in the distance for me personally.
Yes, it was. It was surprisingly fun.
I want to do it again.
Feelings of summer.
I'm going to call everyone.
I know what songs feel like in the summer.
I want to launch it with flowers someday.
That's nice.
I keep saying that.I've been saying it for a long time.
I've been saying this since I arrived in Japan, as if it were a dream.
I still haven't been able to do it.
And now that the tour has finished 5 shows, tomorrow is the turnaround.
Tomorrow, morning and evening will be decided.
Morning, evening, flower, evening.
It's just a little bit down.
It's too early.
It's too early, everyone.
Let's keep the performance in mind.
Let's do our best for lunch tomorrow.
I'll do my best.
I'm off.
Good, he's so cute.
Tomorrow is Osaka.
I'm here.
Hi, Mocchan, Mocchan.
I want to eat chocolate okonomiyaki.
Yotchan, Yotchan. See you soon.
Let's go to Osaka!
Bye bye.
I don't know why, but when I smile, it sure seems like the world is shining
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy, because otherwise I wouldn't be able to walk.
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying, somewhere I'll get my body wet and cold again.
Someone somewhere must be crying, because I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with them.
I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with you, so I'll go wherever you take me
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for yesterday After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart, a piece of the future is painted and blotted out
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for yesterday, after the rain, the streets are turning colors
When you're lost, just remember the reason why you saw it
I'll try to smile even when it's raining
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye, I was yesterday
The town after the rain, the waves are shimmering
My heart is fine as I've grown accustomed to it, rainbow pools, making a sound.A familiar heart is a sunny pattern Rainbow pools and sounds
I play the rainbow piano
Good-bye Goodbye, Yesterday's Me
After the rain, the city, the waves are shimmering
My heart is like a feather, spilling clouds of tears
I'm wearing a rainbow dress
Please subscribe to our channel!